[
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "も",
    "options": [
      "Mo",
      "Ge",
      "Ra",
      "Ta"
    ],
    "answer": "Mo"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ji",
    "options": [
      "び",
      "で",
      "も",
      "じ"
    ],
    "answer": "じ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "みゃ",
    "options": [
      "Mya",
      "Chu",
      "Su",
      "U"
    ],
    "answer": "Mya"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "he",
    "options": [
      "い",
      "は",
      "ひゃ",
      "へ"
    ],
    "answer": "へ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "や",
    "options": [
      "De",
      "Mo",
      "Ya",
      "Fu"
    ],
    "answer": "Ya"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "gyo",
    "options": [
      "ぱ",
      "は",
      "ぽ",
      "ぎょ"
    ],
    "answer": "ぎょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "と",
    "options": [
      "Chi",
      "Ho",
      "Mi",
      "To"
    ],
    "answer": "To"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "nya",
    "options": [
      "れ",
      "り",
      "りょ",
      "にゃ"
    ],
    "answer": "にゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ま",
    "options": [
      "Ma",
      "Cho",
      "Ta",
      "Do"
    ],
    "answer": "Ma"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "kyo",
    "options": [
      "みゃ",
      "よ",
      "きょ",
      "じ"
    ],
    "answer": "きょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "よ",
    "options": [
      "Yo",
      "Mya",
      "So",
      "Kyu"
    ],
    "answer": "Yo"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "pyo",
    "options": [
      "ぱ",
      "りょ",
      "ぜ",
      "ぴょ"
    ],
    "answer": "ぴょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぎ",
    "options": [
      "Ho",
      "Ji",
      "Myu",
      "Gi"
    ],
    "answer": "Gi"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "nyo",
    "options": [
      "にょ",
      "ぜ",
      "が",
      "ぎょ"
    ],
    "answer": "にょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ど",
    "options": [
      "O",
      "Do",
      "Be",
      "Bo"
    ],
    "answer": "Do"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "yu",
    "options": [
      "せ",
      "ゆ",
      "りゃ",
      "る"
    ],
    "answer": "ゆ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "お",
    "options": [
      "Bo",
      "Sa",
      "O",
      "Fu"
    ],
    "answer": "O"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ki",
    "options": [
      "ぱ",
      "き",
      "にゃ",
      "ご"
    ],
    "answer": "き"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "れ",
    "options": [
      "Ma",
      "Ba",
      "Hi",
      "Re"
    ],
    "answer": "Re"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ho",
    "options": [
      "む",
      "ほ",
      "ん",
      "ま"
    ],
    "answer": "ほ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "す",
    "options": [
      "Su",
      "Cho",
      "Se",
      "Zu"
    ],
    "answer": "Su"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "bi",
    "options": [
      "も",
      "ね",
      "び",
      "じゃ"
    ],
    "answer": "び"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ちゃ",
    "options": [
      "Bi",
      "Fu",
      "Cha",
      "Me"
    ],
    "answer": "Cha"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "za",
    "options": [
      "づ",
      "りゅ",
      "ざ",
      "ぢ"
    ],
    "answer": "ざ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ば",
    "options": [
      "Do",
      "Ke",
      "Shu",
      "Ba"
    ],
    "answer": "Ba"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "u",
    "options": [
      "ぬ",
      "う",
      "ら",
      "て"
    ],
    "answer": "う"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ろ",
    "options": [
      "Pa",
      "Nya",
      "Pya",
      "Ro"
    ],
    "answer": "Ro"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "shu",
    "options": [
      "しゅ",
      "じ",
      "へ",
      "さ"
    ],
    "answer": "しゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "あ",
    "options": [
      "Ru",
      "Nya",
      "A",
      "Hya"
    ],
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "pi",
    "options": [
      "ぴ",
      "ぎ",
      "ま",
      "げ"
    ],
    "answer": "ぴ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "りょ",
    "options": [
      "Ryo",
      "Ji",
      "Ne",
      "Ju"
    ],
    "answer": "Ryo"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "gyu",
    "options": [
      "みょ",
      "ぷ",
      "ぎゅ",
      "に"
    ],
    "answer": "ぎゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ひゅ",
    "options": [
      "Hyu",
      "He",
      "Pyo",
      "Ro"
    ],
    "answer": "Hyu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "pya",
    "options": [
      "や",
      "ぴゃ",
      "け",
      "く"
    ],
    "answer": "ぴゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ひゃ",
    "options": [
      "De",
      "Ki",
      "Hya",
      "Yo"
    ],
    "answer": "Hya"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "bya",
    "options": [
      "びゃ",
      "よ",
      "ざ",
      "ゆ"
    ],
    "answer": "びゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "じゅ",
    "options": [
      "Byo",
      "Ke",
      "Kyo",
      "Ju"
    ],
    "answer": "Ju"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "be",
    "options": [
      "べ",
      "じゅ",
      "ぴゃ",
      "ね"
    ],
    "answer": "べ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ご",
    "options": [
      "Pe",
      "Hyo",
      "Go",
      "Te"
    ],
    "answer": "Go"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "nu",
    "options": [
      "ひゃ",
      "ぬ",
      "ちゃ",
      "ば"
    ],
    "answer": "ぬ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぴゅ",
    "options": [
      "Ne",
      "Pyu",
      "Hyo",
      "Mi"
    ],
    "answer": "Pyu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "mu",
    "options": [
      "みゃ",
      "む",
      "え",
      "にゃ"
    ],
    "answer": "む"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "きゃ",
    "options": [
      "Chi",
      "Se",
      "Kya",
      "U"
    ],
    "answer": "Kya"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "rya",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃ",
      "み",
      "りゃ",
      "け"
    ],
    "answer": "りゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ひょ",
    "options": [
      "Ba",
      "Ro",
      "Ma",
      "Hyo"
    ],
    "answer": "Hyo"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ta",
    "options": [
      "ゆ",
      "しゃ",
      "ぼ",
      "た"
    ],
    "answer": "た"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "げ",
    "options": [
      "Ge",
      "Byu",
      "Do",
      "Ha"
    ],
    "answer": "Ge"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ke",
    "options": [
      "せ",
      "きゃ",
      "ちょ",
      "け"
    ],
    "answer": "け"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "びょ",
    "options": [
      "Byo",
      "Hyo",
      "No",
      "Zu"
    ],
    "answer": "Byo"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "wa",
    "options": [
      "も",
      "りゅ",
      "わ",
      "な"
    ],
    "answer": "わ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "み",
    "options": [
      "Pu",
      "Za",
      "Mi",
      "Ji"
    ],
    "answer": "Mi"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "de",
    "options": [
      "で",
      "と",
      "む",
      "ぎょ"
    ],
    "answer": "で"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "こ",
    "options": [
      "Hyo",
      "Cha",
      "Ko",
      "Ne"
    ],
    "answer": "Ko"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "chu",
    "options": [
      "しょ",
      "か",
      "ちゅ",
      "も"
    ],
    "answer": "ちゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぱ",
    "options": [
      "Ri",
      "Zu",
      "Byo",
      "Pa"
    ],
    "answer": "Pa"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ze",
    "options": [
      "き",
      "は",
      "ぜ",
      "ち"
    ],
    "answer": "ぜ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ちょ",
    "options": [
      "Ki",
      "Su",
      "Jo",
      "Cho"
    ],
    "answer": "Cho"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "byu",
    "options": [
      "びゅ",
      "や",
      "ざ",
      "ひ"
    ],
    "answer": "びゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぐ",
    "options": [
      "Ta",
      "Gu",
      "Pi",
      "Myo"
    ],
    "answer": "Gu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ja",
    "options": [
      "ら",
      "じゃ",
      "び",
      "びゅ"
    ],
    "answer": "じゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "そ",
    "options": [
      "Ho",
      "Ja",
      "Tsu",
      "So"
    ],
    "answer": "So"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "zo",
    "options": [
      "ぞ",
      "ひょ",
      "しょ",
      "た"
    ],
    "answer": "ぞ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "しゃ",
    "options": [
      "Myu",
      "Sha",
      "Za",
      "Mya"
    ],
    "answer": "Sha"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "te",
    "options": [
      "みょ",
      "て",
      "き",
      "れ"
    ],
    "answer": "て"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぼ",
    "options": [
      "Chu",
      "Hi",
      "Bo",
      "Kya"
    ],
    "answer": "Bo"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ku",
    "options": [
      "びゅ",
      "い",
      "ら",
      "く"
    ],
    "answer": "く"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "づ",
    "options": [
      "O",
      "Sha",
      "Zu",
      "Ku"
    ],
    "answer": "Zu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "zu",
    "options": [
      "しゃ",
      "づ",
      "ず",
      "しょ"
    ],
    "answer": "ず"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぽ",
    "options": [
      "Ma",
      "Po",
      "Ju",
      "Ri"
    ],
    "answer": "Po"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ka",
    "options": [
      "ぷ",
      "み",
      "か",
      "びょ"
    ],
    "answer": "か"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "せ",
    "options": [
      "Bya",
      "Ryu",
      "Se",
      "E"
    ],
    "answer": "Se"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ra",
    "options": [
      "ら",
      "ぶ",
      "ど",
      "ぴゅ"
    ],
    "answer": "ら"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "な",
    "options": [
      "Na",
      "Sa",
      "De",
      "Pe"
    ],
    "answer": "Na"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "tsu",
    "options": [
      "しゃ",
      "ちょ",
      "づ",
      "つ"
    ],
    "answer": "つ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "りゅ",
    "options": [
      "Ba",
      "Bi",
      "Rya",
      "Ryu"
    ],
    "answer": "Ryu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "pu",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃ",
      "ぷ",
      "ぶ",
      "び"
    ],
    "answer": "ぷ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "し",
    "options": [
      "Kyo",
      "Pi",
      "Shi",
      "Re"
    ],
    "answer": "Shi"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "da",
    "options": [
      "しょ",
      "じ",
      "だ",
      "よ"
    ],
    "answer": "だ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "みゅ",
    "options": [
      "Pa",
      "Myu",
      "Te",
      "Bo"
    ],
    "answer": "Myu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ri",
    "options": [
      "こ",
      "じゅ",
      "ぴ",
      "り"
    ],
    "answer": "り"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぎゃ",
    "options": [
      "Rya",
      "Gya",
      "Ni",
      "Go"
    ],
    "answer": "Gya"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ni",
    "options": [
      "しゅ",
      "わ",
      "に",
      "げ"
    ],
    "answer": "に"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "が",
    "options": [
      "He",
      "I",
      "Ga",
      "Go"
    ],
    "answer": "Ga"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "chi",
    "options": [
      "は",
      "ち",
      "びゃ",
      "お"
    ],
    "answer": "ち"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぺ",
    "options": [
      "Pe",
      "Su",
      "O",
      "Ku"
    ],
    "answer": "Pe"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "sho",
    "options": [
      "しょ",
      "じょ",
      "か",
      "ぴ"
    ],
    "answer": "しょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "め",
    "options": [
      "Ku",
      "Byo",
      "Bi",
      "Me"
    ],
    "answer": "Me"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "bu",
    "options": [
      "ぽ",
      "ぶ",
      "る",
      "ぴ"
    ],
    "answer": "ぶ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ぢ",
    "options": [
      "Be",
      "To",
      "Ne",
      "Ji"
    ],
    "answer": "Ji"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "jo",
    "options": [
      "ふ",
      "さ",
      "ぴょ",
      "じょ"
    ],
    "answer": "じょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "る",
    "options": [
      "Ke",
      "Ru",
      "Ka",
      "Pe"
    ],
    "answer": "Ru"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "sa",
    "options": [
      "ふ",
      "しゅ",
      "さ",
      "つ"
    ],
    "answer": "さ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ね",
    "options": [
      "Rya",
      "Bi",
      "Ku",
      "Ne"
    ],
    "answer": "Ne"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "ha",
    "options": [
      "ぷ",
      "へ",
      "は",
      "しゃ"
    ],
    "answer": "は"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ふ",
    "options": [
      "Zu",
      "Fu",
      "Pya",
      "De"
    ],
    "answer": "Fu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "no",
    "options": [
      "ちゃ",
      "の",
      "りゃ",
      "お"
    ],
    "answer": "の"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ん",
    "options": [
      "Za",
      "Go",
      "Na",
      "N"
    ],
    "answer": "N"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "wo",
    "options": [
      "そ",
      "を",
      "ま",
      "い"
    ],
    "answer": "を"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "きゅ",
    "options": [
      "Pyo",
      "Re",
      "Kyu",
      "Gya"
    ],
    "answer": "Kyu"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "myo",
    "options": [
      "みょ",
      "しゅ",
      "ま",
      "ぴょ"
    ],
    "answer": "みょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "え",
    "options": [
      "Bo",
      "E",
      "Zo",
      "Ju"
    ],
    "answer": "E"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "i",
    "options": [
      "い",
      "め",
      "し",
      "ぽ"
    ],
    "answer": "い"
  },
  {
    "type": "hiragana-to-romaji",
    "prompt": "ひ",
    "options": [
      "Mo",
      "Byo",
      "Ho",
      "Hi"
    ],
    "answer": "Hi"
  },
  {
    "type": "romaji-to-hiragana",
    "prompt": "nyu",
    "options": [
      "か",
      "にゅ",
      "ゆ",
      "しゃ"
    ],
    "answer": "にゅ"
  }
]